Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 1. CDs, 1982-2014
    - Commercial CD, 1982-2014
      - Clockwork Orange - Complete Original Score, 1998; CD-3782; Carlos, Wendy; East Side Digital (Box 20)
        ESD 81362
      - Sonic Seasonings, 1998; CD-3778-3779; Carlos, Wendy; East Side Digital (Box 20)
        ESD 81372
      - Tales of Heaven and Hell, 1998; CD-3795; Carlos, Wendy; East Side Digital (Box 20)
        ESD 81352
      - Beauty in the Beast, 1986; CD-3796; Carlos, Wendy; Jem Records, Inc. (Box 20)
        SYNCD 200
      - Switched on Bach 2000, 1992; CD-3776; Carlos, Wendy; Telarc (Box 20)
        CD-80323
      - The Look Of Love - The Burt Bacharach Collection, 2001; CD-3956-3957; Carpenters; Warwick, Dionne; Como, Perry; Robbins, Marty; Thomas, B.J.; Franklin, Aretha; Shirelles, The; Drifters, The; Jones, Tom; McDaniels, Gene; Pitney, Gene; Hunt, Tommy Burth Bacharach Orchestra and Chorus, The; Radcliff, Jimmy; Vinton, Bobby; Searchers, The; Benton, Brook; Stylistics, The; Jackson, Chuck; Warner Strategic Marketing; 2xCD (Box 72)
        9548-39624-2
      - Holodomor 1932-1933, 2007-11; CD-3630; Cerezo, Joan (Box 16)
      - Kievska 23, 2006; CD-3631; Cerezo, Joan (Box 16)
      - Theremin, 2002; CD-3691; Chiaki, Rom (Box 15)
      - Gloomy Sunday - Tribute, 2002-05; CD-3692; Chiaki, Rom; Natsuaki, Fumihisa (Box 15)
      - Ruby 3: The Invisible World, Part One, 1990; CD-3766-3770; Clark, Tim; ZBS Foundation (Box 20)
        ZBS R3ACD
      - Ruby 3: The Invisible World, Part Two, 1990; CD-3771-3775; Clark, Tim; ZBS Foundation (Box 20)
        ZBS R3BCD
      - Letter accompanying CD-3766-3775, 2001-08-17; Clark, Tim (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Zuihitsu, 2001; CD-3732; Coleman, James; Sedimental (Box 15)
        SEDCD30
      - Complete the Circle, Undated; CD-3654; Compuphonic (Box 16)
      - Letter accompanying CD-3654, 2004-07-02; Compuphonic; Fraser, Nicky; Robertson, Stuart (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Radio Gals - Original Cast Recording, 1995; CD-3544; Craver, Mike; Hardwick, Mark; Varese Sarabande (Box 16)
        VSD-5604
      - Le complex de la viande, 2003; CD-3648; Dailleau, Laurent; Pey, Serge; Repecaud, Dominique (Box 16)
      - Postcard accompanying CD-3648, 2003; Dailleau, Laurent (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Niceâ¦Nice, Undated; CD-3589; Davis, Stanley; Dog World Records (Box 16)
        DWR 98301
      - Power of One, 1989; CD-3704; De Benedictis, Paul (Box 15)
        deBMCD-001
      - Masques, 1992; CD-3718; Denis Moog (Box 16)
        SCY 193
      - Synthology, Undated; CD-3623; Deuchst, Michel; Saphir Records (Box 16)
        192008 M
      - Woman in Darkness, 1999; CD-3614; Deutsch, Herbert A.; 4-Tay Inc. (Box 16)
        4TAY-CD-4012
      - Page One, 1995; CD-3967; Diary, The; Orangewerks (Box 72)
        CDWRK.2.01
      - Rhythm Science in da XXI, Undated; CD-3610; DJ Spooky (Box 16)
      - From A to Z, 1993; CD-3666; Dockstader, Tod; Dresher Paul; Kasinskas, Joseph; Lukasik, Joseph; Z. Pamela; Amirkhanian, Charles; Bimstein, Phillip Kent; Starkland (Box 16)
        ST-203
      - Effector, 2000; CD-3598; Download; Nettwerk Productions (Box 16)
      - First Performances, 2007; CD-3787; Eaton, John; Electronic Music Foundation Ltd. (Box 20)
        EMF CD 056
      - Synthesizer Von Gestern, 1994; CD-3659; Elektronische Musik Aus Köln; Originalton West (Box 16)
        OW019
      - Mars Attacks! Soundtrack, 1996; CD-3694; Elfman, Danny; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 15)
        Atlantic 8299-2
      - Ionisation, Theremin Concerto, 2000; CD-3639; Fuleihan, Anis; Symposium Records (Box 16)
        Symposium 1253
      - World Without Rules, 1996; CD-3740; Haslinger, Paul; RGB Records (Box 20)
        RGB 504-2
      - Dr. Samuel J. Hoffman and the Theremin, 1999; CD-3626-3628; Hoffman, Samuel J.; BASTA Audio/Visuals (Box 16)
        BASTA 30-9093-2
      - Perspectives of New Music, 1987; CD-3664; Hostetler, Randolph; Babbitt, Milton; Swift, Richard; Amirkhanian, Charles; Nimbus Records (Box 16)
        PNM 26
      - Sliver of a Sun, 1999; CD-3976; Izz; Doone Records (Box 72)
        DR1-2233
      - Press kit accompanying CD-3976, 1999; Izz; Doone Records (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Tragedi in the Mangky, 1999; CD-3677; Jerseyband (Box 16)
      - Denshi On, 2006; CD-3615; Kagawa, Eri Li; Ubukata, Noritaka; Hachidai Corporation (Box 16)
        Includes letter from Kagawa to Moog
      - Cultures Electroniques 3, 1988; CD-3668; Kaufmann, Dieter; Dhomont, Francis; Pongrácz, Zoltán; Le Chant du Monde (Box 16)
        LDC 278048
      - Music from the Ether, 1999; CD-3730; Kavina, Lydia; Mode Records (Box 15)
        Mode 76
      - Concerto per Theremin, 2000; CD-3724; Kavina, Lydia; Teleura (Box 15)
        T-CDA-001
      - All That Moog! Part One, Undated; CD-3644; Kingsley, Gershon (Box 16)
      - Mrs. Lenin (Electro-Acoustic Music From The Theremin Center), 1995; CD-3729; Kossenko, Sergey; Stoyanova, Albina; Campos, Jorge; Ponomaryov, Aleksander; Beluntsov, Valery; Smirnov, Andrei; Nikolaev, Vladimir; Yuspova, Iraida; SoLyd Records (Box 15)
        SLR 0044
      - Gymnopedie, 2000; CD-3736; Kurstins, The; Rouge Records (Box 20)
      - No Boundaries, 2004; CD-3799; Ladysmith Black Mambazo; English Chamber Orchestra; Gothoni, Ralf; Head Up International; Gallo Record Company (Box 20)
        HUCD 3092
      - Live from the Outskirts, 2004; CD-3657; Lance, Cyril; DogTalk Music (Box 16)
        DTM0304
      - Music from SEAMUS - Volume 7, 1998; CD-3747; Lopez, Tom; Rice, William; Hamilton, Bruce; Nelson, Jon Christopher; Ingalls, Matt; Hackbarth, Glenn; Society for Electro-Acoustic Music in the United States, The (Box 20)
        EAM-9801
      - Letter accompanying CD-3747, 1998-05-20; Wyatt, Scott A. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Meet the Lothars, Undated; CD-3645; Lothars, The; Camera Obscura; Wobbly Music (Box 16)
        CAM018CD/TOTTER001
      - Happy Holidays, Undated; CD-3646; Lothars, The; Wobbly Music (Box 16)
        TOTTER003
      - Valis, 1988; CD-3705; Machover, Tod; Bridge Records, Inc. (Box 15)
        BCD 9007
      - Discovery: Garaj Mahal and Fareed Haque Present the Moog Guitar, Undated; CD-3601; Mahal, Garaj; Haque, Fareed (Box 16)
      - Movin' On, 1991; CD-3663; Manelsdorff, Albert; Elite Special (Box 16)
        CDJ 76357
      - Let it Go sampler, 1988; CD-3597; Marlo, Clair; Sheffield Lab, Inc. (Box 16)
      - Time Slips Away, 2001; CD-3738; Masami, Takeuchi; Next Records (Box 20)
        NXCD-0010
      - Live, 2001; CD-3960; Mats/Morgan; Ultimate Audio Entertainment (Box 72)
        UAE disc 13
      - Radio Da Da, 1998; CD-3964; Mats/Morgan; Ultimate Audio Entertainment (Box 72)
        UAE DISC 9
      - The Music Or The Money..., 1997; CD-3954-3955; Mats/Morgan; Ultimate Audio Entertainment; 2xCD (Box 72)
        UAE DISC 7
      - The Teenage Tapes, 1998; CD-3952; Mats/Morgan; Ultimate Audio Entertainment (Box 72)
        UAE DISC 10
      - Trends And Other Diseases, 1996; CD-3965; Mats/Morgan; Ultimate Audio Entertainment (Box 72)
        UAE DISC 1
      - Black Black Magic, 2002; CD-3741; Messer Chups; Solnze Records (Box 20)
        SCD025
      - Friday the 13th - The Series soundtrack, 1989; CD-3710; Mollin, Fred; GNP Crescendo Records (Box 15)
        GNPD 8018
      - Letter accompanying CD-3710, 1989-12-19; Mollin, Fred (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Space Galleon, 1997; CD-3633; Moog Poets (Box 16)
      - Original Electronic Neo-Classical Music: The Gig Tape, 2010; CD-3600; Moog, Robert; Abbott, Michael; Lewis, Dan; Bob Moog Foundation (Box 16)
      - Like a Duck to Water, 2001; CD-3790; Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co.; Cuneiform Records (Box 20)
        RUNE 147
      - Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co., 1970-73, 1999; CD-3785; Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co.; Cuneiform Records (Box 20)
        RUNE 109
      - Music by David Borden, 2003; CD-3791; Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co.; Borden, David; Arbiter of Cultural Traditions Inc. (Box 20)
        Arbiter 136
      - The Continuing Story of Counterpoint Parts 9-12, 1988; CD-3793; Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co.; Borden, David; Cuneiform Records (Box 20)
        Rune 16
      - Joyeux Mutato, 1999; CD-3655; Mothersbaugh, Mark; Mutato Muzika; Rhino Entertainment Company (Box 16)
        RHM2 7712
      - Niun Niggung, 1999; CD-3572; Mouse on Mars; Sonig; Rough Trade Records; Our Choice (Box 72)
        RTD 195.3611.2
      - Planetes O.S.T., 2003; CD-3745; Nakagawa, Kotaro; Victor Entertainment (Box 20)
        VICL-61235
      - The Dark Side of the Moog, Undated; CD-3635; Namlock, Pete; Schulze, Klaus; Missing CD; case and insert only (Box 16)
        LC 6269
      - Studies for Player Piano Vol. V, 1988; CD-3667; Nancarrow, Conlon; Wergo (Box 16)
        WER 60165-50
      - The Wild Thornberrys Movie - Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, Undated; CD-3547; Neumann, Drew; Silverline (Box 16)
      - Electronica/Intell Sampler, 1998; CD-3622; Nexus 7; Starcrash Records (Box 16)
        SCR0015
      - Electronic Dance Music, 1993; CD-3674; Nikolais, Alwin; Composers Recordings, Inc. (Box 16)
        CD 651
      - AlieNation, 2004; CD-3629; NYC Reggae Collection; Benchwarrant Records (Box 16)
      - Välling & Fotogen, 1998; CD-3959; Öberg, Mats; G.U.B.B.; Ultimate Audio Entertainment (Box 72)
        UAE disc 8
      - Tranz Party, 1999; CD-3971; One Ring Zero; Planetary Records (Box 72)
        Planetary 9012
      - Letter accompany CD-3971, 1999-09-19; One Ring Zero; Hearst, Michael (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - As Smart As We Are, 2004; CD-3752; One Ring Zero (Box 20)
      - Letter accompanying CD-3752 and SR-26253, Undated; One Ring Zero; Hearst, Michael (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Music from Six Continents, 1992; CD-3548; Ovens, Douglas; Lorentzen, Bent; Verrando, Giovanni; Constantinides, Dino; Fortner, Jack; Vienne Modern Masters (Box 16)
        VMM3009. Includes letter from Douglas Ovens to Moog.
      - Letter accompanying CD-3548, 1994-03-04; Ovens, Douglas (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - The Vortex: Quantum Gate II soundtrack, 1994; CD-3693; Pacheco, Candice; RGB Records (Box 15)
        RGB502-2
      - The Amazing Pop Sound of Jean Jacques Perrey, 1993; CD-3781; Perrey, Jean Jacques; King Record Co., Ltd. (Box 20)
        KICP 338
      - Circus of Life, 2001; CD-3788; Perrey, Jean Jacques; PHMP, LLC. (Box 20)
        MSPH-2028
      - Note accompanying CD-3788, 2004; Perrey, Jean Jacques (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Moog Indigo, 1993; CD-3586; Perrey, Jean Jacques; Vanguard Records, Inc.; King Record Co., Inc. (Box 16)
        KICP 339
      - Magical Moods of the Theremin, 2003; CD-3619; Project: Pimento; Tru Blu Records (Box 16)
      - Dracula - The Seduction, 2000; CD-3616; Proteus 7; Dorian Recordings (Box 16)
        xCD-90283
      - Moods, 2000; CD-3656; Pulauskas, Dainius (Box 16)
        DP-3
      - Theremin, Undated; CD-3642; Ra, Armen (Box 16)
      - The Dream Wanderers, 1997; CD-3609; Rhythm Method; C and S Records (Box 16)
      - Alaska, 1993; CD-3678; Riemann, Kurt; Nightwork Records (Box 16)
        42259-2
      - Gaia, 1998; CD-3679; Riemann, Kurt; Nightwork Records (Box 16)
        KWR42258
      - Dick Robinson pieces 2003-4, 2003-2004; CD-3624; Robinson, Dick (Box 16)
      - Electroacoustic Music Vol. 1, Undated; CD-3641; Robinson, Dick (Box 16)
      - Electroacoustic Music Vol. 2, Undated; CD-3599; Robinson, Dick (Box 16)
      - The Art of the Theremin, 1987; CD-3789; Rockmore, Clara; Delos International, Inc. (Box 20)
        D/CD 1014
      - Clara Rockmore's Lost Theremin Album, 2006; CD-3582; Rockmore, Clara; Reisenberg, Nadia; Bridge Records, Inc. (Box 16)
        BRIDGE 9208
      - The Art of the Theremin, 1987; CD-3581; Rockmore, Clara; Reisenberg, Nadia; Delos International, Inc. (Box 16)
      - The Art of the Theremin, 1987; CD-3625; Rockmore, Clara; Reisenberg, Nadia; Delos International, Inc.; Missing CD; case and insert only (Box 16)
      - Canciones, Undated; CD-3662; Rodrigo, Joaquin; Blue Moon (Box 16)
        BMCD 2071
      - Die Gefiederte Schlange, 1996; CD-3722; Rühmann, Malte (Box 15)
      - Resonanzen, 1994; CD-3658; Sala, Oskar; Originalton West (Box 16)
        OW 028
      - In Blue, Undated; CD-3675-3676; Schulze, Klaus; ZYX Music (Box 16)
        ZYX 90001-2
      - Theremin Noir, 2000; CD-3731; Schwimmer, Rob; Caine, Uri; Feldman, Mark; November Music (Box 15)
        NVR2005-2
      - Manhattan Research, Inc., 2000; CD-3574-3575; Scott, Raymond; Basta Audio/Visuals (Box 16)
        Basta 90782
      - The Music Of Raymond Scott - Reckless Nights And Turkish Twilights, 1992; CD-3816; Scott, Raymond; Columbia Records (Box 20)
        CK 53028
      - Meditatio in Variatione, 1997; CD-3608; Servi; SERVIsound (Box 16)
        LC 6377
      - Meditatio in Variatione, 1997; CD-3649; Servi; SERVIsound (Box 16)
      - Meditatio In Variatione, 1997; CD-3963; Servi; SERVIsound (Box 72)
        CD 1.14-95-3
      - Det Lyckliga Livet, 2000; CD-3953; Skinny; W Records (Box 72)
        DURCDA 002
      - Native Music Denmark Compilation CD Vol. 2 1998/99, 1998; CD-3743; Soren Lee Trio; Solar Plexus; Ok Nokâ¦Kongo; New Jungle Orchestra; Music Spoken Here; Kasper T's Yakuza Zhuffle; Gone Fishin'; Frank ZappALIVE; Confusion; Acid Is; Native Music Denmark (Box 20)
        NAMuCD 9802
      - Hepp-Demo-Spoerri, 1994; CD-3660; Spoerri, Bruno; Hepp, Hardy (Box 16)
        FFO 05
      - Two Against Nature, 2000; CD-3549; Steely Dan; Giant Records (Box 16)
        Album Advance 2-24719-AB
      - Nothing to Fear: A Rough Mix, Undated; CD-3686; Steinski (Box 16)
        ST1017
      - Preview, 1993; CD-3669; Stettner, Georg; Musique Intemporelle (Box 16)
        876 177-907
      - Zyklus / Kontakte / Klavierstucke V & IX, 2000; CD-3958; Stockhausen, Karlheinz; Caprice Records (Box 72)
        CAP 21642
      - Pulaski Skyway and Album II, 2014; CD-3783; Swansen, Chris; Schoolhouse Press Recordings (Box 20)
      - Pulaski Skyway and Album II, 2014; CD-3784; Swansen, Chris; Schoolhouse Press Recordings (Box 20)
      - Vostok 6, 1999; CD-3573; Swinghammer; Cultural Engineering (Box 16)
        CE1
      - Letter accompanying CD-3573, 1999; Swinghammer, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Cords, 1997; CD-3604; Synergy; Third Contact (Box 16)
      - Electronic Realizations for Rock Orchestra, 1995; CD-3612; Synergy; Third Contact (Box 16)
        3CR 1001
      - Reconstructed Artifacts, 2002; CD-3591; Synergy; Third Contact (Box 16)
        3CR 1010
      - Sequencer, 1996; CD-3611; Synergy; Third Contact (Box 16)
        3CR 1002
      - Tagg, 1999; CD-3647; Tagg, Ron; Greenfield Records (Box 16)
        61399-5
      - テルミンを弾く, Undated; CD-3972; Takeuchi, Masami; Gakuyosha; Theremin instruction book/CD (Box 72)
        isbn4-907737-41-6
      - Time to Echolocate, 2005; CD-3632; The Ebb and Flow; Three Ring Records (Box 16)
        TRR007
      - Yes We Didn't, Undated; CD-3584; Thelonious Moog; Grown Up Records (Box 16)
        2072-06-13
      - Saved Gangsta, 1997; CD-3725; Touie; Big B Entertainment (Box 15)
      - Film Music, 1990; CD-3576; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; New World Records (Box 16)
        80389-2
      - Film Music, 1990; CD-3577; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; New World Records (Box 16)
      - Country Moog and Nashville Gold, 2003; CD-3543; Vroom Sound; Trythall, Gil (Box 16)
        VRCD-3330
      - Great African Moments, 1994; CD-3700; Whalen, Michael; Narad Cinema (Box 15)
        ND-66006
      - Phantom of the Forest, 1994; CD-3699; Whalen, Michael; Narad Cinema (Box 15)
        ND-66007
      - Sea Power: A Global Journey, 1993; CD-3698; Whalen, Michael; Narad Cinema; Missing CD; case and insert only (Box 15)
        ND-66005
      - Letter accompanying CD-3698-3700, 1994-02-01; Whalen, Michael (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Cy-fi Symphony, 1994; CD-3621; Yamaoka, Sho; Lemi (Box 16)
      - You Were Spiraling, 1997; CD-3550; Hello Recordings Club (Box 16)
        hel-610
      - Delusions of Grandeur, Undated; CD-3551; You Were Spiraling (Box 16)
      - Engage the Enzyme, 2002; CD-3723; Young M.C.; Stimulus Records (Box 15)
      - Minimoog Classics, 1995; CD-3643; Back In Time Records (Box 16)
      - Mooged Out, Undated; CD-3602; Bob Moog Foundation (Box 16)
      - Ohm: The Early Gurus of Electronic Music: 1948-1980, 2000; CD-3578-3580; Ellipsis Arts (Box 16)
        CD 3670
      - Gdansk, 2003; CD-3651; Gdansk Recordings (Box 16)
        LATO 001
      - Moog: Original Film Soundtrack, 2004; CD-3637-3638; Hollywood Records, Inc. (Box 16)
      - Plug In and Turn On, 1994; CD-3652-3653; Instinct Records (Box 16)
        EX-267-2
      - Best of Moog, 1999; CD-3634; Loud Records (Box 16)
      - Best of Moog, 1999; CD-3733; Loud Records (Box 20)
      - Shake Demo, Undated; CD-3684; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 16)
      - Various Assets: Not for Sale, 2005; CD-3671-3672; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 16)
      - Various Assets: Not for Sale, 2005; CD-3682-3683; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 16)
      - The Moog Cookbook, 1996; CD-3587; Restless Records (Box 16)
        72914-2
      - Royer Microphone Tests, 1999-12-28; CD-3673; Sear Sound (Box 16)
      - The Impact of Electricity on Music, 2005; CD-3590; Wire, The; CBC Radio (Box 16)
    - Non-Commercial CD, 1988-2004
      - Ich!, 2001; CD-3751; Austronaut G.; Emotion Entertainment (Box 20)
      - The Galaxy of Sound, Undated; CD-3763; Blue Chip Orchestra (Box 20)
      - Cayuga Night Music, 2004; CD-3804; Borden, David; Lameduck Music (Box 20)
      - Earth Journeys, 1999; CD-3806; Borden, David; Lameduck Music (Box 20)
      - Liner notes accompanying CD-3806, 1999; Borden, David (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Earth Journeys 4, 2001; CD-3805; Borden, David; Lameduck Music (Box 20)
      - Smart Hubris, 2004; CD-3803; Borden, David; Lameduck Music (Box 20)
        K216.01
      - Anthology, Undated; CD-3808-3809; Borden, David (Box 20)
      - Heaven-Kept Soul from the Anagram Portraits, 2004; CD-3800; Borden, David (Box 20)
      - Recent Work, 2002; CD-3807; Borden, David (Box 20)
      - Unmatched David Borden notes, 1999-2004; Borden, David (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - A Concerto for eViolin and Synthesizer Ensemble, 2003; CD-3810; Borden, David; Davids, Martin (Box 20)
      - Setude, Undated; CD-3952; Botermans, Wilco (Box 72)
      - Demo material from forthcoming album, Undated; CD-3690; C., Alvin (Box 15)
      - Letter accompanying CD-3709, 2000-06-26; Cibola (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Virgin of Macarena, 2000; CD-3709; Cibola (Box 15)
        Oklahoma City, Oklahoma
      - Show 330 - Spies, 2002; CD-3606; Fishko, Sara; Studio 360 (Box 16)
      - Fishko Files -Theremin - Public Radio Show, 2001-05-24; CD-3593; Fishko, Sara (Box 72)
      - A Theremin Christmas, 1999; CD-3762; Franklin, Virgil (Box 20)
      - Powerfield Music Video CD, Undated; CD-3607; Gallivan, Joe; Jenkins, Carl Lyle (Box 16)
      - J. Dimenna mixes for Bob Moog, 2004-10-04; CD-3553; Heller, Steven (Box 16)
      - Cool Rhythms, Undated; CD-3748; HKB (Box 20)
        HKBCD6
      - Into the Ether- Theremin Radio Shows - Pt. 1 and 2, 2003-11; CD-3757-3758; Hypnotique (Box 20)
      - Session Project Demo 2003, 2003; CD-3761; Hypnotique (Box 20)
      - Theremin: Eri Li, 2003-10-12; CD-3583; Kagawa, Eri Li (Box 16)
      - From the Sublime to the Ridiculous, 2002; CD-3801; Kingsley, Gershon; Kingsley Sound, Inc. (Box 20)
      - All that Moog! Part Two, Undated; CD-3594; Kingsley, Gershon (Box 16)
      - Theremin; Series g4A, Undated; CD-3750; Masami, Takeuchi (Box 20)
      - Everything You Always Wanted to Hear on the Moog, Undated; CD-3585; Mighty Moog, The (Box 16)
      - Galactic, Undated; CD-3706; Moog, Robert; Robinson, Siobhan (Box 15)
      - Legion of Mary, Undated; CD-3712; Moog, Robert; Robinson, Siobhan (Box 15)
      - Mixed CD, Undated; CD-3707; Moog, Robert; Robinson, Siobhan (Box 15)
      - Mixed CD, Undated; CD-3708; Moog, Robert; Robinson, Siobhan (Box 15)
      - Like a Naked Man to Water: The Mother Mallard Basement Tapes, 2004; CD-3802; Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece Co.; Lameduck Music (Box 20)
      - Bob Moog - Interview for The Wire - CBC Radio - Complete and Unedited, Undated; CD-3759; Pietropaolo, Paolo; CBC Radio (Box 20)
      - Excerpts from Soundtracks, 2004; CD-3703; Rhodes, Bill (Box 15)
      - Music for Escher, Undated; CD-3552; Rhodes, Bill (Box 16)
        Includes note from Rhodes to Moog
      - Privately recorded theremin performances, 2003; CD-3680; Rosen, Lucie; Holmes, Thom (Box 16)
        Includes letter from Thom Holmes to Moog
      - Solder Joint, 2003; CD-3546; Soldadura (Box 16)
      - Mary Sparks, Undated; CD-3697; Sparks, Mary (Box 15)
      - Crafting Sound, Undated; CD-3617-3618; Spitzer, Nick; American Routes (Box 16)
        AR 02-16
      - Beg, Borrow, and Steal: A Steinski Archive, Undated; CD-3605; Steinski (Box 16)
      - Odyssey of Analogy, 2000; CD-3726-3727; Svenska Analogsympatisörer (Box 20)
        SAS CD #5
      - Stadt und Stau Wald und Wiese, Undated; CD-3764-3765; Svenska Analogsympatisörer (Box 20)
        SAS#4
      - Swedish Hotsynth Quintet, Undated; CD-3588 (Box 16)
      - Emi Takanabe's performance of theremin, Undated; CD-3713; Takanabe, Emi (Box 15)
        MiniDisc
      - A Tribute to Moog, 1998; CD-3749; Thompson, Robert Scott; Gresham, Mark; Fried, Neil; Pfeiffer, Jodene; Duncan, Steve; Hulse, Steve; Robinson, Rick; Hyett, Mark; Horst, Eddie; Johnson, Lee; Lagrange College Department of Music Annual Electronic Music Festival (Box 20)
      - Ideal Lady, 1999; CD-3711; Unicorn; Platform Music (Box 15)
      - Shangle Music Promo, Undated; CD-3968; Venant, Henrik (Box 72)
      - Delayhoelle, 2001; CD-3681; Voiceheads; Tripbeat Foundation (Box 16)
      - Supperstar Synths - Audio Demo - Reunion - NAMN, 2000; CD-3696; Wakefield, Kevin (Box 15)
        NAMN 2000
      - Nova Luna, 2001; CD-3702; Wilhelm, David; Particle Storm Digital Productions (Box 15)
      - Track list/art accompanying CD-3702, 2001; Wilhelm, David; Particle Storm Digital Productions (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - 3 tracks of stuff that's fun for stargazing, Undated; CD-3701 (Box 15)
      - BFD samples - Confidential, Undated; CD-3542 (Box 15)
      - Examples of music using Moog synthesizers, Undated; CD-3595 (Box 16)
      - Moog Inspired: Synthesizers and Theremins, Undated; CD-3603 (Box 72)
      - Moog SDTK, Undated; CD-3592 (Box 16)
      - Snofkin for Bob and Miranda, Undated; CD-3636 (Box 16)
      - Switched on Radio with Bob Moog - Discs 1 and 2, 2004-07; CD-3753-3754 (Box 20)
      - Switched on Radio with Bob Moog - Discs 1 and 2, 2004-07; CD-3755-3756 (Box 20)
      - Unknown music CD, Undated; CD-3620 (Box 16)
      - Unlabeled TDK CD-R74, Undated; CD-3714 (Box 15)
      - Unlabeled TDK CD-R74, Undated; CD-3715 (Box 15)
      - Unlabeled TDK CD-R74, Undated; CD-3716 (Box 15)
  - 2. Magnetic Tape, 1954-2002
    - Commercial Cassette, 1974-2000
      - 8:30, 1979; tr-16336; Weather Report; CBS Inc. (Box 15)
        P2T 36030
      - Spiel mit auf der Melodica, 1974; tr-16726; Hören und Spielen; Music Records; Hohner (Box 20)
      - Booklet accompanying tr-16726, 1974; Hören und Spielen (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Tron: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1982; tr-16672; Carlos, Wendy; CBS Records (Box 21)
        SMT 37782
      - Brooklyn Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, 1983; tr-16518; Foss, Lukas; Gramavision Records (Box 21)
        GRC-7006
      - Digital Moonscapes, 1984; tr-16132; Carlos, Wendy; CBS Records (Box 10)
        MT 39340
        New York, New York
      - Celebrate Freedom, 1984; tr-16154; Driscoll, Phil; The Sparrow Corporation; Mighty Horn Records (Box 10)
        SPC 1094
        Cleveland, Tennessee
      - New England, 1985; tr-16383; Griner, Clyde; Terra; Vanguard Recording Society (Box 15)